snapbid.in 2012-06-08

# Snapbid Privacy Policy

**SnapBid** respects your privacy and assures you that any information provided by you to **SnapBid** is protected and will be dealt with according to this Policy. To avail of the Services offered on SnapBid.in, you may have to provide certain information to us. This includes your:  
1\. Username  
2\. Password  
3\. Valid Email address  
4\. Name  
5\. Birth Date  
6\. Postal address/Contact details  
7\. Phone number  
**SnapBid** does not encourage direct communication between users who use the Services, rather has in place a system where SnapBid passes information meant for you from other users through a relay system thus screening your personal/contact information from potentially malicious users.

Hence, you are requested not to give any personal information and/or contact details including your phone numbers (mobile or otherwise) and email address in Content you may post and which is viewable to others on the Website. This is to protect your privacy and to restrict communication which may possibly be unwanted/offensive/malicious/obscene or communication which may be otherwise be intrusive to you. In the event that you still disseminate such information or even otherwise, you understand and acknowledge that SnapBid will not be liable in any manner if you become the recipient of communication which you may find unwanted/offensive/malicious/obscene or otherwise intrusive.

When you visit SnapBid.in, certain information may also be automatically collected and stored, including:  
1\. The IP address of your computer, browser type and language.  
2\. The date and the time during which you accessed the site.  
3\. The address of the website which you may have used to link to SnapBid.in  
When you visit SnapBid.in, cookies may be left in your computer. A cookie is a small text file that uniquely identifies your browser. The cookies assigned by the servers of SnapBid may be used to personalize your experience on SnapBid.in. Additionally, cookies may also be used for authentication and security purposes.

Cookies may also be assigned by the advertisers of SnapBid when you click on any of the advertisements which may be displayed on SnapBid.in in which case such cookies are controlled by these advertisers and not SnapBid.  
**  
SnapBid** may also use software applications for website traffic analysis and to gather statistics, used for advertising and for determining the efficacy and popularity of SnapBid.in among others.  
Information gathered by SnapBid is stored securely using several information security applications including firewalls. However, security is always relative and SnapBid cannot guarantee that its security measures are absolute and cannot be breached.  
Also, data which is transmitted over the Internet is inherently exposed to security risks or threats. For instance, information transmitted via chat or email can be compromised and used by others. Therefore, SnapBid cannot guarantee any security for such information.  
When you register with SnapBid, your account is protected by means of login information which includes a username and a password that is known only to you. Therefore, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your login information including your username and password. If you become aware of or reasonably suspect any breach of security, including compromise of your login information, it is your responsibility to immediately notify SnapBid.

**SnapBid** communicates with you through email address that you would have specified at the time of registration. SnapBid may use this email address to send you emails related to the proper functioning of your account for instance when you receive a response to a advertisement/classified you have posted on SnapBid or to send you newsletters that you have subscribed or to send you occasional announcements about changes in SnapBid’s policies or promotions introduction of new services. It is possible that such emails may contain commercial messages of advertisers. To Un-subscribe from any such promotional mailer sent by the SnapBid, you/user need to click on relevent link/button shown on the emailer to unsubscribe from the promotinal database. This may take upto 48 hrs/2 working days to process.  
SnapBid.in may contain links to other websites. Such websites are governed by their own privacy policies and SnapBid does not exercise any control over them. It is your responsibility to read and understand the privacy policy of such websites when you follow a link outside SnapBid.  
**  
SnapBid** has a policy of not sharing any personally identifiable information with anyone other than entities specifically authorized by SnapBid which may include advertisers and sponsors of SnapBid. However, SnapBid may use cumulative non-personal information for auditing and analysis purposes with the aim of improving its services. Additionally, SnapBid may share personally identifiable information if sharing of such information is necessary:  
1\. to comply with legal processes or governmental request, or  
2\. to enforce the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, or  
3\. for prevention of fraud, or  
4\. for issues involving information security, or  
5\. to protect  
a. your rights;  
b. the rights of SnapBid; and  
c. the rights of the general public

**SnapBid** confirms that this Privacy Policy is only a description of its operation regarding user information. This Policy is not intended to and does not create any legal rights in your favour or in the favour of any other person. SnapBid reserves the right to change this policy at any time without giving you prior notice.
